blushybabe.com 2019-01-06

# PRIVACY - Blushy Babe

Updated May 23, 2018 to reflect GDPR compliance standards

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally identifiable information’ (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website. We honor your right to privacy and will comply with your wishes to remove your data from our systems.

### What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address or other details to help you with your experience.

### When do we collect information?

We collect information from you when you register on our site or enter information on our site.

### How do we use your information?

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

  * To improve our website in order to better serve you.
  * To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
  * To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.

### How do we protect visitor information?

How do we protect visitor information?

 **We do not use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards.**

  * We use regular Malware Scanning.

### Do we use ‘cookies’?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

We use cookies to:

  * Understand and save user’s preferences for future visits.
  * Keep track of advertisements.
  * Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third party services that track this information on our behalf.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser’s Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

If you disable cookies off, some features will be disabled It won’t affect the users experience that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly.

However, you can still access the website .

### Third Party Disclosure

Do we disclose the information we collect to Third Parties?

Some information, such as IP and your email address, may be shared with the following third parties who help us run our website and email programs. They will only use this information to serve our needs and are prohibited from using it in any other instance. They are (but not limited to):

  * Google (ad serving and website tracking)
  * Facebook ( Pixel tracking and Serving Ads )

### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### Google

Google’s advertising requirements can be summed up by Google’s Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users.  
<https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en>

We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

We have implemented the following:

  * Remarketing with Google AdSense

We along with third-party vendors, such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions, and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

 **Opting out:**  Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising initiative opt out page or permanently using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.

### Data collected by advertisers

Each time you visit the website, third party advertisers and advertising companies, including Google, may collect personal and other information, through your IP address, and by using technology such as cookies. Advertisements appearing on the website are delivered to you by third party advertisers, often based on what you do on various websites. This is sometimes referred to as behavioral advertising, or contextual advertising. Third party advertisers and advertising companies use information about you (not including your name or email address), including your IP address and cookies collected through your use of websites, to provide advertisements on this website about goods and services that may be of interest to you. The use of this information collected by third party advertisers and advertising companies through this website is not covered by this privacy policy and Worify Media is not responsible for the use of this information by third parties.

### COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation’s consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online.

We do not specifically market to children under 13.

### CAN SPAM Act

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

To be in accordance with CANSPAM we agree to the following:

  * NOT use false, or misleading subjects or email addresses
  * Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way
  * Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters
  * Monitor third party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.
  * Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly
  * Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email

If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can

  * Follow the instructions at the bottom of each email.

and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) .

  1. **Data we use**

When you register to use or use our services we collect and store or process the following information for the purposes described as shown in the following table:  

**Type of Data**

| 

 **Purpose of processing**  
  
---|---  
  
Name

| 

Identification of you as a human being and customer; valid for registered users and comments only.  
  
User-ID

| 

Administration of users, valid for registered users only.  
  
IP-Address

| 

Evaluation of which countries our service is used from and fraud protection. Used to identify you as a person.  
  
DeviceID

| 

Only stored when using this site on a mobile device: this helps us to know you are viewing from a mobile device and adapting technical parameters such as screen size accordingly.  
  
Geolocation data

| 

Used to determine from which country you are viewing to determine language and ad settings as well as for fraud protection.  
  
Cookie ID

| 

Cookies are used to identify you as a person and thereby ensuring that only relevant ads are shown to you.  
  
  1.  **Your rights**

In accordance with GDPR, Section III, articles 12 to 21, you have the following rights, of which we hereby inform you as follows:  

  * You have the right to be informed on how we use your data:  
This information is provided in section 2 of this Privacy Statement. Should you have any further questions, please, do not hesitate to get in contact with us (cf. below, section VI, for contact details).  

  * You have the right to know who your counterpart is:  
Worify Media Ltd, Kemp House, 160 City Road London, EC1V 2NX   

  * You have the right to know for how long we store your data:  
Your data will be stored as long as you don’t close account or for as long as you continue to use this site as an unregistered user. If you stop using this site, your data will be deleted 3 years after your last use.  
If no legal proceedings are pending at the time of account closure, your data will be deleted 3 years after account closure or after last use. In case of pending legal proceedings your data will be deleted once these legal proceedings are completed.  

  * You have the right to complain to a data protection authority:  
If you are an EU citizen or EU resident, please complain to the EU data protection authority of your home country. Before complaining, please, get in contact with us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#8ee2ebe9efe2cef9e1fce7e8f7a0ede1e3) , we shall try to settle all disputes amicably first.  
If you are not a resident or EU citizen, please note that none of the rights above apply to you including your right of complaint.

  * You have the right to ask us about what data we store:  
In order to make use of this right, please get in contact with us as stated in point VI.  

  * You have the right of correction:  
If you feel or know that the data we store about is incorrect, let us know. We will correct any errors as soon as possible.

  * You have the right of deletion:  
You have the right that we delete all your data if you close your account or if you withdraw your consent.

  * You have the right of restriction of processing:  
If you want to make use of this right, get in contact with us.

  * You have the right of data transferability:  
You have the right to receive your basic data in an electronic format for transfer to another provider. Data will be provided in XML-format.

  * You have the right to withdraw consent:  
You can withdraw your consent anytime, but this will result in your being shown less relevant advertising. If you want to withdraw consent, please get in contact with us via email. By withdrawing your consent, Processing of your personal data will stop immediately after we processed your request.  

  1. **Point of contact**

Your point of contact for all questions, requests, or concerns is:[[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). For making use of your right to information about data stored you need to send us or any form of ID that includes your name, your date of birth, and a photo.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to [contact us](https://blushybabe.com/contact).

At BlushyBabe.com we consider the privacy of our visitors to be extremely important. This privacy policy document describes in detail the types of personal information is collected and recorded by BlushyBabe.com and how we use it.

 **Online Privacy Policy Only**  
This privacy policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website and regarding information shared and/or collected there. This policy does not apply to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.

#### Comments

when visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

#### Media

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

#### Cookies

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

#### Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

#### What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

#### Where we send your data

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

 **Consent**  
By using our website, you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms.

 **Update**  
This Privacy Policy was last updated on Wednesday, May 23rd, 2018.  
_Should we update, amend or make any changes to our privacy policy, those changes will be posted here._

>  **DISCLOSURE POLICY**

This policy is valid from May 23rd, 2018.  
This blog is a collaborative blog written by a group of individuals. This blog accepts forms of cash advertising, sponsorship, paid insertions or other forms of compensation.

This blog abides by word of mouth marketing standards. We believe in honesty of relationship, opinion and identity. The compensation received may influence the advertising content, topics or posts made in this blog. That content, advertising space or post will be clearly identified as paid or sponsored content.

The owner(s) of this blog is not compensated to provide opinion on products, services, websites and various other topics. The views and opinions expressed on this blog are purely the blog owners. If we claim or appear to be experts on a certain topic or product or service area, we will only endorse products or services that we believe, based on our expertise, are worthy of such endorsement. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer or provider.

This blog does contain content which might present a conflict of interest. This content may not always be identified.
